ebookmall.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Statement - eBookMall

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for eBookMall (<http://www.ebookmall.com/>).

**Orders**

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (like a name and email address) and financial information (like a credit card number). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders.

Information provided for eBook orders is used only to complete eBook orders. This information will never be used for any purpose except to complete the eBook order.

**Submission Form / Publishing Center**

Users of the eBookMall Publishing Center will occasionally receive information directly related to the Publishing Center. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

Communications for processing requested Publishing Center products, services, and/or orders may require communication by email, fax, or phone.

We request information from the user on our Submission form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name, phone, billing and email address) as well as information about the manuscript or eBook.

Information provided for eBook orders is used only to complete the eBook publishing process. This information will never be used for any purpose except to complete the eBook publishing process.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Sharing**

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use third party services such as Verisign and Bank of America to process and complete orders. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Affiliates**

Many companies affiliated with eBookMall use eBookMall to process orders. Personally identifiable customer information is never shared with companies affiliated with eBookMall. We do not and will not provide any personally identifiable customer information to our affiliates.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that eBookMall is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by eBookMall as well as all orders processed by eBookMall.

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users must selectively choose to receive our newsletter. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out by replying to the email with "unsubscribe" or "remove" in the subject line or unsubscribing at the Newsletter Subscription page.

**Reviews**

eBookMall reserves the right to edit, crop, or modify all book reviews. The review a user submits becomes the property of eBookMall. If it is selected to be posted on the website, it will appear sometime in the near future. If posted, we only post the information the reviewer provided when submitting the review.

 **Notification Requests**

If a user wishes to be notified about specific products and/or services, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users must selectively choose to receive this information. Users who no longer wish to receive our notifications may opt-out by replying to "unsubscribe" or "remove" in the subject line in the email.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code or age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry: SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security, privacy practices, and ALL employees have signed a non-disclosure agreement legally binding them keep secret all proprietary company information including customer information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can [contact us](http://www.ebookmall.com/help-desk/customer-service-form).

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as the email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done within the user's eBookMall account or by [contacting us](http://www.ebookmall.com/customer-service).

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.
